Phone: (+91) 9259293858 8630863750

Email: aarifsaifi731@gmail.com
Address: 136A, Mohalla Bhrampuri
Muradnagar, Ghaziabad

AARIF SAIFI

Objective

2+ Years of Progressive Experience working as a UI Developer. Knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJs. Good Programming and good Problem-Solving ability. To work in a challenging atmosphere by exhibiting my skills with utmost sincerity dedicated smart work for the growth of your esteemed organization along with mine.

Technical Skills

HTML5, CSS3, JAVASCRIPT, REACTJS, REDUX

Work Experience

Embronic Technosoft, Noida, Sector 9 - 2018 - 2020

September 2018 – November 2020

Education

St. Giri Higher Secondary. Inter College, Meerut – High School

Year 2010, Percentage 60%

K. N. MODI Inter College, Modinagar - High School

Year 2012, Percentage 50%

Choudhary Charan Singh University, Meerut - B.C.A.

Year 2012-2015, Percentage 62.5%

Abdul Kalam Technical University, Lucknow – M.C.A.

Year 2015-2017, Percentage 75%

PROJECTS

Argola Cosmetique - https://argolacosmetique.com/
Leading the front-end development on the completely re-designed core landing
② Developing highly modularized and advanced object-oriented (oop) design in JavaScript to ensure reusability, extensibility, and ease of maintenance.
Pramework built-in client-side optimization with minified js/CSS with svg sprites or data-uri.
☑ Test-driven development (tdd) with jasmine and karma for unit-testing and code.
2 Automated documentation and tutorial using jsdoc, markdown.
Managing and conducting the development of multiple ongoing projects.
Horscircuits- http://www.horscircuits.ca/
Environment html4/html5, css2/css3, JavaScript, jQuery, reactJS, ajax, json.
② As a part of the horscircuits.ca team developed reusable components, plugins, libraries and adoptive responsive interfaces.
② Worked on a development team which included other technical professionals, subject matter experts, project stakeholders and executive leadership.
② Developed web applications with a focus on, but not necessarily limited to, the front-end development implementation.
G.R.I.S - https://www.greenribboninternationalschool.com/
Environment html4/html5, css2/css3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap.
② As a part of the Greenribboninternationalschool.com team developed reusable components, plugins, libraries and adoptive responsive interfaces.
② Worked on a development team which included other technical professionals, subject matter experts, project stakeholders and executive leadership.
② Developed web applications with a focus on, but not necessarily limited to, the front-end development implementation.

Vertex Plus Elevators - http://vertexpluselevators.com/

Developing highly modularized and advanced object-oriented (oop) design in JavaScript to ensure reusability, extensibility, and ease of maintenance.

- Pramework built-in client-side optimization with minified js/CSS with svg sprites or data-uri.
- 2 Test-driven development (tdd) with jasmine and karma for unit-testing and code.

PERSONAL PROFILE

D.O.B. – 12 JULY 1995
Father's Name – Zakir Husan
Languages – Hindi, English
Nationality – Indian
Sex - Male
Hobbies – Play Cricket, Listening Music

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the above-mentioned details are true to the best of my knowledge.

Date Name:- AARIF SAIFI